[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the summer months, a clock located in Indianapolis, IN, USA will show a different time than a clock located in Paducah, KY.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Arsenic and Old Lace, John Alexanders character Teddy Brewster thinks he is who?", "correct_answer": "Theodore Roosevelt", "incorrect_answers": ["Teddy Bear", "Abraham Lincoln", "Jefferson Davis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these foods is generally poached in white wine?", "correct_answer": "Fish", "incorrect_answers": ["Fruit", "Eggs", "Poultry"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What town do they take Ben Wade to catch the 3:10 train in the western movie 3:10 to Yuma?", "correct_answer": "Contention", "incorrect_answers": ["Dodge City", "Yuma", "Sweet Water"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A pure diamond is colorless, but extremely rare. This is the color shade that most diamonds have.", "correct_answer": "Yellow", "incorrect_answers": ["Gray", "Blue", "Green"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 2003s movie Johnny English Rowan Atkinson starred alongside this beautiful Australian singer.", "correct_answer": "Natalie Imbruglia", "incorrect_answers": ["Missy Higgins", "Kylie Minogue", "Dannii Minogue"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Onions will not prove beneficial for treating which of the following conditions?", "correct_answer": "Stomach ulcer", "incorrect_answers": ["Boils", "Common cold", "Osteoporosis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Academy Award-winning author and screenwriter is best known for his 1969 novel about the Mafia which he later co-adapted into a film directed by Francis Ford Coppola", "correct_answer": "Mario Puzo", "incorrect_answers": ["James Ellroy", "Salvatore Quasimodo", "Tony Ardizzone"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following countries and states shares its name with its capital city?", "correct_answer": "Luxembourg", "incorrect_answers": ["New York", "Malta", "Oklahoma"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who portrayed Harry Potter in each film of the Harry Potter series?", "correct_answer": "Daniel Radcliffe", "incorrect_answers": ["Richard Harris", "Tom Felton", "Rupert Grint"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Polar bears are among penguins\u2019 most dangerous natural enemies.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the live action film Casper what was the last name of the family that befriended Casper?", "correct_answer": "Harvey", "incorrect_answers": ["Smith", "Reinhold", "McEvoy"]}]